Jocselyn Aguilar

Full Stack Engineer with experience in Python, Django, Angular and Docker. I also have knowledge of Java, Spring Boot, React and AWS. I am Proactive and adaptable. I seek to continue growing professionally and contribute my skills to challenging projects.

Costa Rica(Heredia)

(506) 6339-91-35

jocselynaguilarchinchilla@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jocsely n-aguilar-a85749251/

EXPERIENCE

EEDS, Remote: Front-End Engineer

May 2023-November 2023

Web application created using Angular 13 together with libraries such as Bootstrap and Angular Material. Direct work with the client to collect requirements and model the application.

4Geeks, Remote: Internship Full Stack Engineer

August 2023-October 2023

Full stack development with Python, Django and Angular. My responsibilities included learning and implementing these technologies to improve the company's main web application. As part of these improvements, technologies such as Typesense were applied and the development of a function in GCP capable of communicating with OpenAI for resume analysis. We worked with the Scrum methodology to manage the project.

Limbo, Remoto: Apprentice and Volunteer in Full Stack Engineering

April 2022-August 2023

As a volunteer and apprentice of the program, I led the development of a web application from the beginning, dedicating time to acquiring skills in the technologies to be used, including GraphQL, React, Typescript and NodeJS. I also had the responsibility of imparting my knowledge to new students in the program, and I also held the role of instructor at Cenfotec University, covering topics such as object-oriented programming and programming fundamentals.

EDUCATION

Cenfotec University, San josé: *Bachiller in Software Engineering*

January 2021-December 2024

University training focused on practical programming and engineering projects, focused on collaborative work and the adoption of good development practices.

APTITUDES

Autodidact.

Disciplined.

Consistent.

Passionate.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Bloom Web application designed and created to help people suffering from anxiety, integrated with a panic button, so that users could ask for help when needed.

Cenfoteco Kingdoms Desktop game using design patterns in Java, LibGDX was used for the application interface. This game was chosen to be presented at the university's Maker Fest in June 2023.

Waze of thrones Project created in C++, using non-linear data structures, mainly using the Dijkstra graph algorithm.

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English